[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tom Cruise starred opposite this Hollywood actress in the 1992 movie Far and Away.", "correct_answer": "Nicole Kidman", "incorrect_answers": ["Daryl Hannah", "Meg Ryan", "Kim Basinger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Olivieri brothers, Pat and Harry, are given credit  for inventing this in 1933.", "correct_answer": "The Philly cheesesteak", "incorrect_answers": ["Dental floss", "The jet engine", "The McDonald quarter-pounder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Narwhals and belugas make up separate subspecies of cetaceans. However, taxonomists often include in it a dolphin which lives in Indo-Pacific waters. What is the name of this dolphin?", "correct_answer": "Irrawaddy dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["Bottlenose dolphin", "Boto", "Risso\u2019s dolphin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following movie characters says this phrase: Yo, Adrian, its me...?", "correct_answer": "Rocky Balboa", "incorrect_answers": ["John Constantine", "Paulie Pennino", "Adrian Pennino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal character did Bruce Willis voice in the 2006 animated movie Over the Hedge?", "correct_answer": "RJ the Raccoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Vincent the Bear", "Verne the Turtle", "Tiger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By US law, employees do not have to wash hands after sneezing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor in a Leading Role at the 81st Academy Awards 2009?", "correct_answer": "Sean Penn", "incorrect_answers": ["Mickey Rourke", "Frank Langella", "Brad Pitt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where are the main characters of the movie Dawn of the Dead hiding from the hordes of the undead?", "correct_answer": "a Shopping mall", "incorrect_answers": ["a Military Facility", "an Underground bunker", "a House"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 2009 Walt Disney action comedy movie the main characters are guinea pigs.", "correct_answer": "G-Force", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fast and the Furry", "Darwin", "Fluffy Spies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did Russia declare war against Japan during World  War II?", "correct_answer": "Two days after the bombing of Hiroshima", "incorrect_answers": ["The day after the Battle of Kursk", "The day after the Battle of Stalingrad", "Two days after Germany surrendered."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which nation claims ownership of the South Pole?", "correct_answer": "No nation does.", "incorrect_answers": ["Russia", "France", "The USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The badger can be found in every part of the lower 48 states.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]